[
	{
		"question": "In CSS, how would you select a div tag with a class of container?",
		"answer": "div.container",
		"choices": [
			"container.div",
			"div#container",
			".container#div"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which javascript condition is truthy?",
		"answer": "1 == true",
		"choices": [
			"true === 'true'",
			"0 == 'false'",
			"'1' === true"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which javascript condition is truthy?",
		"answer": "(!(true && false) && (false || true))",
		"choices": [
			"!(!(true && true) || true)",
			"((true || true) && !(true && true))",
			"!(true && !false)"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which of the following does NOT trigger when the document is ready?",
		"answer": "$(document).on('ready', () => {/* ... */})",
		"choices": [
			"$(document).ready(() => {/* ... */})",
			"$(function() {/* ... */})",
			"$('document').ready(function() {/* ... */})"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "HTML stands for",
		"answer": "Hyper Text Markup Language",
		"choices": [
			"Hyper Text Modul Language",
			"Hyper Test Markup Language",
			"Hyperlink Markup Language"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "Where we can use the <style> tag?",
		"answer": "In the <head> and <body> elements",
		"choices": [
			"In the <head> element",
			"In the <body> element",
			"In neither the <head> nor the <body> elements"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "How do you write an HTML Comment?",
		"answer": "<!-- This is an HTML comment -->",
		"choices": [
			"// This is an HTML comment",
			"/* This is an HTML comment */",
			"** This is an HTML comment **"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "What HTML form input must be used to present multiple options, but select only one?",
		"answer": "<input type=\"radio\">",
		"choices": [
			"<input type=\"text\">",
			"<input type=\"checkbox\">",
			"<input type=\"submit\">"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the HTML form input used to send information of the form to the server?",
		"answer": "<input type=\"submit\">",
		"choices": [
			"<input type=\"server\">",
			"<input type=\"send\">",
			"<input type=\"mail\">"
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "How you can open the link in a new window?",
		"answer": "target=\"_blank\"",
		"choices": [
			"target=\"_new\"",
			"target=\"_window\"",
			"target=\"_tab\""
		]
	},
	{
		"question": "CSS stands for",
		"answer": "Cascading Style Sheets",
		"choices": [
			"Computer Style Sheets",
			"Creative Style Sheets",
			"Canvas Styling System"
		]
	}
]